Rustie (Ting-Chi) Lin

43311 Jerome Ave. Fremont, CA 94539

(510) 676 0295 rustielin@berkeley.edu

https://github.com/rustielin https://www.linkedin.com/in/rustie-ting-chi-lin-a74 50199

Summary

Resourceful worker with diverse experience in computer software and hardware, social media, marketing, workflow, and leadership.

Recognized by peers as diligent, hardworking, and dedicated to projects from inception to finished product.

Fast learner and open minded; constantly pursuing unique approaches to problems from a variety of perspectives.

Work Experience

Android Developer, Geeni, Org.

Berkeley, CA — Jan 2017 - Present

- Android application development
- Exercised efficient workflow using git version control
- Used Firebase, Cloud messaging, Google Login Authenticaion, file storage, Volley, Stripe, etc.

Software Developer, TileWarp, Inc.

Fremont, CA — Apr 2016 - Sept 2016

- Android game development
- Managed workflow and changes to source code

Intern, Pijjit, LLC

San Francisco, CA — June 2014 - Oct 2015

- Handled incoming queries
- Reached out to journalists for media coverage
- Launched successfully funded KickStarter campaign

Education

University of California, Berkeley
— Computer Science and Statistics, 2020
Mission San Jose High School (MSJHS)
— 3.8 GPA (unweighted), 2016

Skills

Leadership

- Mission San Jose Odyssey of the Mind Program (President, Vice President)
- MSJHS Science for Youth (Vice President)
- MSJHS Marching Band and Tri-City Band Corps. (Rank Captain and Section Leader)
- Huang Leadership Development Scholarship recipient

Computer Programming (projects)

- Cal Hacks 3.0 mouse control via hand tracking and gestures using OpenCV
- OutsideHacks IV Location coordinator app and shared map for concert goers
- Silicon Valley CodeDay 2015 —Best Multiplayer Award — 2D Pong game with real-time remote control from twitch.tv
- UC Berkeley BearHacks 2016 First Place — pseudo-Snapchat filter
- Fall 2016 HackJam Root chord approximator for music files
- CodeDay SF Winter 2015 mobile app to help music students memorize their scales
- Los Altos Hacks 2016 meditative and elegant virtual note-pad

Hobbies

- Linux/GNU and open source software
- Art and Music
- Cooking and baking
- Early morning exercise
- Organizing mini "hackathons" for friends and classmates